[text "Re"] slides in from the left 21px (slide+fade), linear, 400ms
[text "R"] slides in from the left 36px (slide+fade), ease-out, 1502ms
[text "Re"] slides out to the right 46px (slide), linear
[text "emembering"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~104ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 21px, linear
[text "is so"] slides in from the right 22px (slide+fade), ease-out, 333ms
[text "Remembering s so"] slides out to the left 46px (slide), ease-in
[text "vesterday"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~42ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 114px, ease-out
[text "Meet"] letters cascade in ~33ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 97px, ease-out
[text "vesterday"] slides out to the right 21px (slide), ease-in
[text "Meet"] pops out
[text "your"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~67ms apart (pop), ease-out
[text "your"] slides out up-left 223px (slide), ease-in
[text "New"] fades in as one block, linear, 400ms
[text "app"] slides in rising 128px (slide), linear, 433ms
[text "notes"] slides in rising 53px (slide), linear, 267ms
[text "es pp"] slides out to the left 158px (slide), linear
[text "second"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~56ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 261px, ease-out
[text "brain"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~117ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 91px, ease-out
[text "r"] slides in from the right 204px (slide), ease-out, 1635ms
[text "econd brain"] slides out to the left 246px (slide), ease-in
[text "thought"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~93ms apart (slide), each sliding from the right 252px, ease-out
[text "patner"] letters cascade in right-to-left ~150ms apart (pop), each sliding from the right 57px, ease-out
[text "hought artner"] slides out down-left 152px (slide), ease-in
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "Capture anything"] pops in
[text "apture anything"] slides out to the right 9px (slide), ease-in
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "Turn brain dumps into beautiful"] letters cascade in ~139ms apart (pop), each dropping 11px, ease-out
[text "Turn brain dumps into beautiful"] pops out
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "meeting"] fades in as one block, linear, 400ms
[text "Let Mem take"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~33ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 79px, ease-out
[text "et Mem ta"] slides out to the left 38px (slide), ease-out
[text "for you"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~67ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 37px, ease-out
[text "for you"] slides out to the right 33px (slide), ease-out
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "Tel"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~34ms apart (slide+fade), each rising 51px, ease-out
[text "Tel"] pops out
[text "nd ak"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~156ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 174px, linear
[text "to"] slides in from the right 127px (slide+fade), ease-in, 3537ms
[text "Tell"] pops in
[text "ell"] pops out
[text "need"] slides in rising 49px (slide), ease-out, 2936ms
[text "ee s aout"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~89ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 136px, ease-in
[text "th doin ne"] letters cascade in ~95ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 74px, ease-out
[text "b"] slides in from the right 154px (slide), linear, 1168ms
[text "I e ma am"] letters cascade in right-to-left ~300ms apart (slide), each sliding from the right 32px, ease-out
[text "eed"] slides out up-left 62px (slide), ease-out
[text "need to ask about the domain name"] slides out upward 37px (slide), ease-in
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "Mem"] slides in rising 13px (slide+fade), ease-out, 133ms
[text "remembers"] slides in up-left 22px (slide), ease-out, 767ms
[text "Mem"] slides out to the left 23px (slide), ease-out
[text "membe"] slides out to the left 10px (slide), ease-out
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "Find"] slides in from the right 13px (slide), ease-out, 133ms
[text "Find"] slides out to the right 36px (slide), linear
[text "e"] slides in from the right 86px (slide), linear, 734ms
[text "Deep Sarch"] letters cascade in right-to-left ~8ms apart (slide+fade), linear
[text "Deep Search"] leaves at hard cut
[cut] hard cut
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "d"] slides in from the right 105px (slide), ease-in, 1168ms
[text "an"] slides in from the right 51px (slide+fade), ease-out, 200ms
[text "ve"] slides in dropping 45px (slide), ease-out, 1701ms
[text "recall"] fades in as one block, ease-out, 167ms
[text "and recall"] fades out (167ms)
[text "everything"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~52ms apart (slide+fade), ease-out
[text "every"] pops in
[text "every ve"] slides out to the left 17px (slide), linear
[text "everything"] slides out to the left 11px (slide), ease-in
[text "Mem Chat"] fades in as one block, linear, 634ms
[text "Mem Chat"] fades out (300ms)
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "I've created a to-do list for you"] letters cascade in ~33ms apart (slide+fade), each rising 27px, ease-out
[text "f ce"] slides in up-left 38px (slide+fade), linear, 1234ms
[text "created a to-do list for you"] slides out to the left 32px (slide), ease-in
[text "m Sr"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~251ms apart (slide), each sliding up-right 55px, ease-out
[text "and o ours"] pops in
[text "and of course"] slides out to the left 20px (slide), ease-out
[text "Offline Mode"] slides in from the left 16px (slide), ease-out, 233ms
[text "Tea haing"] slides in up-right 40px (slide), linear, 1067ms
[text "Offline Mode"] slides out upward 40px (slide), ease-in
[text "Team Sharing"] pops out
[text "Templates"] slides in rising 31px (slide), ease-out, 567ms
[text "c"] slides in up-left 39px (slide+fade), ease-out, 1168ms
[text "Templates"] slides out to the left 14px (slide), ease-out
[text "Dark Mode"] letters cascade in ~181ms apart (pop), each rising 17px, ease-out
[text "API Acess"] pops in
[text "API Access"] pops out
[text "Dark Mode"] pops out
[text "Not"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~184ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 118px, ease-out
[text "another"] slides in from the right 62px (slide+fade), ease-out, 433ms
[text "notes"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~25ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 34px, ease-out
[text "Not another notes"] slides out upward 23px (slide), linear
[text "Your"] slides in from the left 21px (slide+fade), ease-out, 534ms
[text "go-to thought"] letters cascade in right-to-left ~79ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the left 23px, ease-out
[text "partner"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~72ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the left 26px, ease-out
[text "Your go-to thought partner"] slides out to the left 9px (slide), ease-in
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)